Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Competitive Advertisements, Pre-55 Group, 1894-1957
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Container List
  - Food Products
    - Crackers
      - McCormicks, 1919-1936 (Box 100)
      - National Biscuit Co., 1949-1954, (6 folders) (Box 100)
      - National Biscuit Co., 1920-1948, (13 folders) (Box 101)
      - National Biscuit Co., 1953 (Box 102)
      - Ry-Krisp, 1942-1953, (11 folders) (Box 102)
      - Sawyer, 1932 (Box 102)
      - Sunshine, 1922-1942, (9 folders) (Box 102)
      - Sun Wheat Biscuits, 1930 (Box 102)
      - Sunshine, 1925-1953, (13 folders) (Box 103)
      - Wheatsworth, 1921-1930 (Box 103)
      - Weston's, 1928-1930 (Box 103)
      - Miscellaneous, 1945 (Box 103)
    - Desserts
      - Gelatin, 1920-1944 (Box 104)
      - Pudding, 1920-1952, (15 folders) (Box 104)
      - Pie and Pie Filling (Box 104)
      - Miscellaneous, 1920-1956, (12 folders) (Box 104)
      - Good Luck, 1930 (Box 104)
      - Pie Crust Maine Maid (Box 104)
      - Cream Whipping Aids, 1949-1954, (5 folders) (Box 105)
      - Cones, 1930 (Box 105)
      - Ice Cream and Ice Cream Mixes (Box 105)
      - Breyer's, 1950 (Box 105)
      - Sealtest, 1950 (Box 105)
      - Miscellaneous, 1950 (Box 105)
      - Chocolate (Box 105)
      - Miscellaneous, 1943-1954, (11 folders) (Box 105)
      - Baker's, 1942 (Box 105)
      - Coconut, 1945-1954, (8 folders) (Box 105)
      - Flavoring Extracts (Box 105)
      - Miscellaneous, 1915-1954, (18 folders) (Box 105)
      - Chocolate, 1927 (Box 105)
      - Desserts (Box 105)
      - Pies and Pie Fillings, 1954 (Box 105)
      - Miscellaneous, 1948-1953, (5 folders) (Box 106)
    - Cream Whipping Aids, 1943-1948, (6 folders) (Box 106)
    - Dairy Products not covered by butter or milk
      - National Dairy Products Corp., 1943-1948, (6 folders) (Box 106)
      - Borden, 1945-1953, (8 folders) (Box 106)
      - Hood's, 1945 (Box 106)
      - Miscellaneous, 1944-1954, (8 folders) (Box 106)
    - Eggs, 1928-1945, (5 folders) (Box 106)
    - Flavoring Extracts, 1949 (Box 106)
    - Pies and Pie Fillings
      - Borden, 1942-1947, (4 folders) (Box 106)
    - Puddings and gelatin
      - Amazo, 1949-1954, (4 folders) (Box 106)
      - Argo, 1940 (Box 106)
      - Gumperts Pudding, 1934-1935 (Box 106)
      - Heinz Mince Meat and Puddings, 1935 (Box 106)
      - Junket, 1943-1952, (7 folders) (Box 106)
      - Jell-O, 1943 (Box 106)
      - Jell-O, 1925-1954, (17 folders) (Box 107)
      - Jell-O, 1951 (Box 108)
      - Junket, 1927-1951, (7 folders) (Box 108)
      - Knox Gelatin, 1939-1941 (Box 108)
      - Kosto Pudding, 1930-1933 (Box 108)
      - Kre-Mel, 1930-1942, (4 folders) (Box 108)
      - Kwik-Set, 1930 (Box 108)
      - Minute Gelatin, 1894-1925 (Box 108)
      - Minute Tapioca, 1925-1941, (4 folders) (Box 108)
      - Minute Tapioca, 1921-1942, (2 folders) (Box 109)
      - My-T-Fine, 1934-1954, (15 folders) (Box 109)
      - Plymouth Rock Gelatine, 1927-1930 (Box 109)
      - Reichardt's Chocolate, 1928 (Box 109)
      - Richardson and Robbins, 1921-1935 (Box 109)
      - Rockwood's Decorettes, 1924-1926 (Box 109)
      - Royal, 1941-1954, (14 folders) (Box 109)
      - Sparkle Gelatin, 1940 (Box 109)
      - Junket, 1953 (Box 109)
      - Jell-O, 1938-1941 (Box 109)
      - Miscellaneous, 1953-1954, (2 folders) (Box 109)
    - Ice Cream and Ice Cream Mixes
      - Abbott's, 1952 (Box 110)
      - Abbottmaid, 1920-1926 (Box 110)
      - Borden's, 1931-1940, (2 folders) (Box 110)
      - Breyer's, 1928-1954, (13 folders) (Box 110)
      - Dixies, 1937 (Box 110)
      - Cardini, 1937 (Box 110)
      - Chapman's, 1931-1932 (Box 110)
      - Fro-Joy, 1928-1937, (2 folders) (Box 110)
      - Hood's, 1932 (Box 110)
      - Horton's, 1918-1934, (4 folders) (Box 110)
      - Hydrox, 1923-1939, (4 folders) (Box 111)
      - Lipton Frostee Dessert Mix, 1951-1952, (2 folders) (Box 111)
      - Meadow Gold, 1931 (Box 111)
      - Midco, 1938 (Box 111)
      - Reid's, 1931-1941, (2 folders) (Box 111)
      - Reick's, 1928-1931 (Box 111)
      - Sealtest, 1944-1954, (6 folders) (Box 111)
      - Smith Bros., 1933 (Box 111)
      - Smoothie, 1933 (Box 111)
      - Sunfreeze, 1933 (Box 111)
      - Southern Dairies, 1927-1936, (2 folders) (Box 111)
      - Sunny Meadows, 1927 (Box 111)
      - Supplee, 1932 (Box 111)
      - Teall's, 1929 (Box 111)
      - Tech, 1931 (Box 111)
      - Velvet, 1930-1931 (Box 111)
      - Cones, 1928-1929 (Box 111)
      - Miscellaneous, 1949-1954 (Box 111)
      - Miscellaneous, 1927-1951, (14 folders) (Box 112)
      - Breyer's, 1953 (Box 112)
      - Sealtest, 1953 (Box 112)
      - Lipton Frostee Dessert Mix, 1953 (Box 112)
    - Flour
      - Pillsbury's Best, 1922-1937, (12 folders) (Box 113)
      - Pillsbury's Best Enriched, 1951-1954, (3 folders) (Box 113)
      - Pillsbury's Cake Flour, 1929-1936, (4 folders) (Box 113)
      - Pillsbury MinitMix, 1937 (Box 113)
      - Pillsbury Pancake Mix, 1922-1939, (10 folders) (Box 113)
      - Pillsbury Semonlina, 1927-1930 (Box 113)
      - Pillsbury Sno-Sheen, 1936 (Box 113)
      - Pillsbury Wheat Bran, 1931 (Box 113)
      - Presto, 1945 (Box 113)
      - Red Band, 1933-1937, (2 folders) (Box 113)
      - Softasilk, 1952-1953, (2 folders) (Box 113)
  - Food Products
    - Flour
      - Pillsbury, 1945 (Box 114)
      - Presto, 1927-1948, (15 folders) (Box 114)
      - Sno Sheen cake flour, 1952 (Box 114)
      - Softasilk, 1947-1951, (5 folders) (Box 114)
      - Jenny Wren, 1927-1929 (Box 114)
      - Stoy soy flour, 1944 (Box 114)
      - Suzanna pancake and waffle flour, 1944 (Box 114)
      - Swan's Down, 1928-1949, (10 folders) (Box 114)
      - Pillsbury pie crust and cake mixes, 1949-1950, (2 folders) (Box 114)
      - Teco, 1927-1928 (Box 115)
      - Virginia Sweet, 1928 (Box 115)
      - Pillsbury pie crust and cake mixes, 1952 (Box 115)
      - Pillsbury hot roll and cake mixes, 1948 (Box 115)
      - Swan's Down, 1929-1954, (6 folders) (Box 115)
      - Pillsbury, 1928-1951, (13 folders) (Box 115)
      - Miscellaneous, 1954 (Box 115)
  - Beverages
    - Coffee
      - Savarin, 1953 (Box 116)
  - Food Products
    - Flour
      - Miscellaneous, 1948-1953, (6 folders) (Box 116)
      - Aunt Jemima, 1940-1954, (13 folders) (Box 116)
      - Cuplets, 1933-1939, (2 folders) (Box 116)
      - Ballard's, 1931-1937, (3 folders) (Box 116)
      - Ceresota, 1933 (Box 116)
      - Betty Crocker, 1954 (Box 116)
      - Ranch House pancake flour, 1944 (Box 116)
      - Drifted Snow, 1942 (Box 116)
      - Dromedary, 1944-1953, (10 folders) (Box 116)
      - Dromedary, 1936-1943, (6 folders) (Box 117)
      - Duff's, 1931-1953, (16 folders) (Box 117)
      - Flako, 1932-1953, (14 folders) (Box 117)
      - Flakorn, 1939-1940, (2 folders) (Box 117)
      - General Mills (Gold Medal, Bisquick), 1941-1945, (5 folders) (Box 117)
      - General Mills (Gold Medal, Bisquick), 1946-1954, (8 folders) (Box 118)
      - Betty Crocker, 1952-1953, (2 folders) (Box 118)
      - General Mills institutional, 1945-1948, (2 folders) (Box 118)
      - General Mills (Gold Medal, Softasilk), 1937-1952, (15 folders) (Box 118)
      - General Mills (Gold Medal, Bisquick), 1950-1954, (4 folders) (Box 119)
      - Gold Medal, 1920-1938, (16 folders) (Box 119)
      - Globe A1, 1942 (Box 119)
      - Occident, 1929-1932, (2 folders) (Box 119)
      - Globe A1, 1930 (Box 120)
      - Golden Wheat Soy, 1944 (Box 120)
      - Golden Soy Griddle, 1943-1944, (2 folders) (Box 120)
      - Hecker's, 1927-1942, (10 folders) (Box 120)
      - Hetty Harper's Brownie Mix, 1935 (Box 120)
      - Jean's, 1937 (Box 120)
      - Jenny Wren, 1931-1934, (2 folders) (Box 120)
      - Joy, 1927 (Box 120)
      - Kitchen Craft, 1942-1944, (2 folders) (Box 120)
      - Minute Biscuit, 1932 (Box 120)
      - Occident, 1914-1952, (4 folders) (Box 120)
      - Purity, 1929 (Box 120)
      - Sno Sheen cake flour, 1949-1951, (2 folders) (Box 120)
      - Pillsbury, 1946-1954, (23 folders) (Box 120)
      - Pillsbury, 1949-1953, (2 folders) (Box 121)
      - Hecker's, 1930 (Box 121)
      - Globe A1, 1931 (Box 121)
      - Gold Medal, 1924 (Box 121)
    - Fruit--Fresh
      - California Fruit Growers (Sunkist), 1923-1953, (15 folders) (Box 121)
      - Chiquita bananas, 1949-1952 (Box 121)
      - Miscellaneous, 1919-1929 (Box 121)
      - California Fruit Growers (Sunkist), 1927-1934, (5 folders) (Box 122)
      - Florida Citrus Commission, 1925-1950, (14 folders) (Box 122)
      - Atwood, 1931-1932 (Box 122)
      - Bananas, 1926-1928 (Box 122)
      - Unifruit bananas, 1927-1928 (Box 122)
      - Banana Growers' Association, 1930 (Box 122)
      - Bartlett pears, 1925 (Box 122)
      - Blue Anchor, 1932 (Box 122)
      - Blue Goose, 1928-1940, (2 folders) (Box 122)
      - Calavo, 1929-1931 (Box 122)
      - California miscellaneous, 1939-1941 (Box 122)
      - California Fruit Growers Exchange, 1927-1935, (2 folders) (Box 122)
      - Canadian apples, 1930 (Box 122)
      - California Fruit Growers Exchange, 1931 (Box 123)
      - Fruit Dispatch Co., 1933-1940, (2 folders) (Box 123)
      - Fruit Industries, 1935 (Box 123)
      - Georgia peaches, 1939 (Box 123)
      - Imperial Valley canteloupes, 1926 (Box 123)
      - Grapefruit, 1934 (Box 123)
      - Indian River, 1931 (Box 123)
      - Jim Hill apples, 1928-1930 (Box 123)
      - Jonathan apples, 1928 (Box 123)
      - Mel-O-Ripe, 1933-1939 (Box 123)
      - Red & Gold vintages, 1932 (Box 123)
      - Seald Sweet, 1927-1931, (2 folders) (Box 123)
      - Skookum apples, 1928-1934 (Box 123)
      - State of Florida, 1936 (Box 123)
      - Strawberries, 1930 (Box 123)
      - Sunkist, 1924-1926 (Box 123)
      - Tru Blu, 1933-1938 (Box 123)
      - United Fruit Co., 1931-1940, (2 folders) (Box 123)
      - Vintner's grapes, 1931 (Box 123)
      - Washington State apples, 1931-1938, (2 folders) (Box 123)
      - Pineapples, 1926-1928 (Box 123)
      - Wenatchee apples, 1923 (Box 123)
      - Miscellaneous, 1931-1954, (11 folders) (Box 123)
      - Miscellaneous, 1944-1946, (3 folders) (Box 124)
    - Ice
      - Knickerbocker, 1928-1935 (Box 124)
      - Union, 1930-1933 (Box 124)
      - Miscellaneous, 1928-1937 (Box 124)
    - Pickles and olives
      - Miscellaneous, 1942-1954, (11 folders) (Box 124)
      - Heinz, 1923-1941 (Box 124)
      - Pimentos, 1939 (Box 124)
      - Sauerkraut, 1928-1932 (Box 124)
    - Popcorn (includes Cracker Jack), 1930-1954, (7 folders) (Box 124)
    - Potato chips and potato salad, 1941-1950, (11 folders) (Box 124)
    - Meat and poultry
      - Poultry, 1932-1954, (12 folders) (Box 124)
      - Wilson, 1949-1950, (2 folders) (Box 124)
      - Mickelberry's, 1930-1933 (Box 124)
      - Beechnut Bacon, 1920-1929 (Box 124)
      - Boned chicken, 1921-1927 (Box 124)
      - Hormel, 1950-1954, (5 folders) (Box 124)
      - Hormel, 1928-1949, (15 folders) (Box 125)
      - Howard's sausage, 1928 (Box 125)
      - Hygrade, 1935-1949, (3 folders) (Box 125)
      - Underwood, 1927 (Box 125)
      - Vogt's, 1916-1925 (Box 125)
      - Jones, 1928-1939, (2 folders) (Box 125)
      - Land-O-Lakes, 1934 (Box 125)
      - Long Island Duckling, 1927-1930 (Box 125)
      - Mor, 1942 (Box 125)
      - Morgan, 1932 (Box 125)
      - Morris, 1928 (Box 125)
      - Morrell, 1942 (Box 125)
      - New England Pork, 1932 (Box 125)
      - Oscar Mayer, 1950-1952, (3 folders) (Box 125)
      - Swift, 1941 (Box 125)
      - Prudence, 1941 (Box 125)
      - Skinless, 1953 (Box 125)
      - Skinless, 1942-1952, (10 folders) (Box 126)
      - Smithfield, 1934-1936 (Box 126)
      - Stahl-Meyer, 1933-1934 (Box 126)
      - Underwood, 1928-1954, (9 folders) (Box 126)
      - Wilson, 1921-1953, (10 folders) (Box 126)
      - Miscellaneous, 1927-1934, (3 folders) (Box 126)
      - Meat extenders and tenderizers, 1953 (Box 126)
      - Miscellaneous, 1939-1954, (13 folders) (Box 127)
      - Miscellaneous, 1950-1954, (2 folders) (Box 128)
    - Cooking fats and shortening
      - Armour, 1920-1936 (Box 128)
      - Cottolene, 1918 (Box 128)
      - Crisco, 1926-1942, (8 folders) (Box 128)
      - Crisco, 1922-1925 (Box 129)
      - Formay, 1932-1933 (Box 129)
      - Prido, 1936 (Box 129)
      - Snowdrift, 1924-1942, (4 folders) (Box 129)
      - Crisco, 1944-1951, (8 folders) (Box 129)
      - Crisco, 1952-1954, (3 folders) (Box 130)
      - Spry, 1939-1954, (14 folders) (Box 130)
      - Miscellaneous, 1948-1954, (7 folders) (Box 130)
      - Miscellaneous, 1943-1947, (5 folders) (Box 131)
      - Crisco, 1943 (Box 131)
    - Soups
      - Campbell's, 1926-1934, (6 folders) (Box 131)
      - Campbell's, 1935-1945, (11 folders) (Box 132)
      - Heinz, 1930-1954, (19 folders) (Box 133)
      - Hormel, 1933-1940, (3 folders) (Box 133)
      - Lipton's, 1950-1954, (5 folders) (Box 133)
      - Lipton's, 1942-1949, (8 folders) (Box 134)
      - Miscellaneous, 1930-1954, (15 folders) (Box 134)
  - Gasoline, Oils and Lubricants
    - Alemite, 1948-1954, (7 folders) (Box 134)
    - Alemite, 1945-1947, (3 folders) (Box 135)
    - Atlantic, 1945-1953, (9 folders) (Box 135)
    - Cities Service, 1953-1954, (4 folders) (Box 135)
    - Conoco, 1946-1953, (6 folders) (Box 135)
    - Ethyl, 1943, 1951, (2 folders) (Box 135)
    - Gulf Oil, 1945-1951, (4 folders) (Box 135)
    - Mobilgas, 1951-1954, (2 folders) (Box 135)
    - Phillips 66, 1951-1954, (2 folders) (Box 135)
    - Union Oil Company of California, 1950 (Box 135)
    - Miscellaneous, 1950-1953, (2 folders) (Box 135)
    - Gulf Oil, 1944-1949, (5 folders) (Box 136)
    - Macmillan Ring-Free motor oil, 1942-1953, (12 folders) (Box 136)
    - Mobilgas, 1944-1953, (5 folders) (Box 136)
    - Pennzoil, 1948-1954, (14 folders) (Box 136)
    - Pennzoil, 1943-1947, (5 folders) (Box 137)
    - Phillips 66, 1946-1953, (7 folders) (Box 137)
    - Quaker State, 1943-1954, (11 folders) (Box 137)
    - Conoco, 1950, 1954, (2 folders) (Box 137)
    - Sinclair, 1951-1954, (3 folders) (Box 137)
    - Texaco, 1951-1954, (2 folders) (Box 137)
    - Gulf Oil, 1953 (Box 137)
    - Standard Oil, Inc., 1954 (Box 137)
    - Cities Service, 1950-1951, (2 folders) (Box 137)
    - Standard Oil Company of California, 1951 (Box 137)
    - Sunoco, 1951 (Box 137)
    - Conoco, 1952 (Box 138)
    - Gulf Oil, 1952 (Box 138)
    - Phillips 66, 1950 (Box 138)
    - Sinclair, 1943-1952, (9 folders) (Box 138)
    - Socony-Vacuum (see also Mogilgas), 1945-1954, (12 folders) (Box 138)
    - Standard Oil, Inc., 1944-1953, (9 folders) (Box 138)
    - Socony-Vacuum (see also Mogilgas), 1943, 1952, (2 folders) (Box 139)
    - Standard Oil, Inc., 1943-1953, (20 folders) (Box 139)
    - Sunoco, 1939-1954, (11 folders) (Box 139)
    - Texaco, 1950-1953, (3 folders) (Box 139)
    - Texaco, 1944-1949, (6 folders) (Box 140)
    - Shell--competitive (various companies), 1943-1946 (Box 140)
    - Tidewater Associated Oil Co. (Tydol--Veedol), 1945-1954, (7 folders) (Box 140)
    - Tidewater Associated Oil Co. (Tydol--Veedol), 1948-1950, (3 folders) (Box 141)
  - Household Goods
    - Cleaners and Cleaning Fluids
      - Boon, 1947 (Box 141)
      - Ethyl, 1947 (Box 141)
      - Miscellaneous, 1947-1954, (7 folders) (Box 141)
      - Windex, 1946-1954, (8 folders) (Box 141)
    - Cleansers and Scouring Compounds
      - Bab-O, 1947-1949, (3 folders) (Box 141)
      - Bon Ami, 1947-1954, (8 folders) (Box 141)
      - Old Dutch Cleanser, 1951-1954, (4 folders) (Box 141)
      - Sunbrite, 1945-1947, (2 folders) (Box 141)
      - Spic & Span, 1947-1954, (7 folders) (Box 141)
      - Miscellaneous, 1952-1953, (2 folders) (Box 141)
      - Old Dutch Cleanser, 1947-1950, (4 folders) (Box 142)
      - Oakite, 1947-1954, (7 folders) (Box 142)
    - Clocks, 1948-1954, (7 folders) (Box 142)
    - Cloths (dish, polishing, etc.), 1950 (Box 142)
    - Cooking Utensils
      - Club Aluminum, 1946-1954, (7 folders) (Box 142)
      - Mirro-Matic, 1946-1954, (9 folders) (Box 142)
      - Ek-Co pressure cooker, 1946-1954, (9 folders) (Box 142)
      - Miscellaneous, 1947 (Box 142)
      - Revere Ware, 1947-1954, (8 folders) (Box 142)
      - Wearever, 1948-1954, (7 folders) (Box 142)
      - Wearever, 1946-1947, (2 folders) (Box 143)
      - Miscellaneous, 1948-1954, (6 folders) (Box 143)
    - Curtains
      - Miscellaneous, 1947-1954, (7 folders) (Box 143)
      - Berkshire, 1949 (Box 143)
    - Dinnerwear (China, Pottery, Plastic, etc.), 1954 (Box 143)
    - Disinfectants
      - Clorox, 1947-1954, (8 folders) (Box 143)
      - Drano, 1947-1954, (8 folders) (Box 143)
      - Lysol, 1947-1954, (6 folders) (Box 143)
      - Sani-Flush, 1947-1954, (8 folders) (Box 143)
      - Miscellaneous, 1949-1953, (4 folders) (Box 143)
      - Miscellaneous, 1947-1950, (4 folders) (Box 144)
    - Dyes
      - Tintex, 1947-1951, (4 folders) (Box 144)
      - Miscellaneous, 1947-1953, (7 folders) (Box 144)
    - Anti-Noise Devices, 1953 (Box 144)
    - Awnings, 1949-1954, (6 folders) (Box 144)
    - Air Cleaners, 1952 (Box 144)
    - Bedding
      - Bedspreads and blankets (Box 144)
      - Miscellaneous, 1946-1954, (8 folders) (Box 144)
      - Sheets and pillowcases
        - Cannon, 1947-1954, (8 folders) (Box 144)
        - Pepperell, 1952-1954, (3 folders) (Box 144)
        - Pequot, 1952-1954, (3 folders) (Box 144)
        - Utica, 1952-1954, (3 folders) (Box 144)
        - Wamsutta, 1951-1952, (2 folders) (Box 144)
      - Mattresses--Simmons Beautyrest, 1948-1954, (7 folders) (Box 144)
      - Sheets and pillowcases (Box 144)
      - Simmons Beautyrest, 1947-1952, (2 folders) (Box 145)
      - Miscellaneous, 1947-1952, (6 folders) (Box 145)
      - Sheets and pillowcases
        - Pacific, 1947 (Box 145)
        - Pepperell, 1947-1951, (5 folders) (Box 145)
        - Pequot, 1948-1951, (4 folders) (Box 145)
        - Utica, 1950 (Box 145)
        - Fieldcrest, 1949 (Box 145)
        - Pillows, 1951 (Box 145)
        - Miscellaneous, 1949-1953, (5 folders) (Box 145)
        - Springmaid, 1950 (Box 145)
      - Bedding miscellaneous, 1948 (Box 145)
      - Bedspreads and blankets, 1949-1953, (5 folders) (Box 145)
      - Sheets and pillowcases
        - Miscellaneous, 1947-1954, (3 folders) (Box 146)
        - Utica, 1948-1949, (2 folders) (Box 146)
        - Wamsutta, 1947-1954, (5 folders) (Box 146)
      - Bedspreads and blankets, 1953 (Box 146)
      - Mattresses
        - Simmons Beautyrest, 1953 (Box 146)
        - Miscellaneous, 1953-1954, (2 folders) (Box 146)
    - Bleach (see also Household--Disinfectants)
      - Climalene, 1945-1950, (5 folders) (Box 146)
      - Clorox, 1946-1954, (9 folders) (Box 146)
      - Miscellaneous, 1943-1953, (11 folders) (Box 146)
    - Bluing
      - Miscellaneous, 1947-1954, (8 folders) (Box 146)
      - Miscellaneous, 1943-1946, (4 folders) (Box 147)
      - Mrs. Stewart's, 1942 (Box 147)
    - Bottles, Thermos, 1947-1954, (8 folders) (Box 147)
    - Brushes, Brooms and Mops, 1943-1953, (7 folders) (Box 147)
    - Candles, 1941-1954, (11 folders) (Box 147)
    - Bulbs, Sparklet, 1943 (Box 147)
    - Chimes, 1946-1949, (3 folders) (Box 147)
    - China and pottery, 1942-1953, (13 folders) (Box 147)
    - Soap and Scouring Powder (See also Cleansers)
      - Bon Ami, 1926-1936, (5 folders) (Box 147)
      - Babbitt's Lye, 1922-1938, (2 folders) (Box 147)
      - Gillett's, 1935-1937 (Box 147)
      - Lewis' Lye, 1920 (Box 147)
      - Rex, 1934 (Box 148)
      - Lye miscellaneous, 1928-1942, (5 folders) (Box 148)
      - Ammo, 1928-1939, (4 folders) (Box 148)
      - Bab-O, 1925-1944, (17 folders) (Box 148)
      - Babbitt's Lye, 1929-1933, (2 folders) (Box 148)
      - Gillett's, 1932 (Box 148)
      - Lewis' Lye, 1932-1934, (2 folders) (Box 148)
      - Be Bright, 1924-1926 (Box 148)
      - Bon Ami, 1937-1946, (9 folders) (Box 148)
      - Bon Ami, 1922-1943, (9 folders) (Box 149)
      - Boraxo, 1936-1938 (Box 149)
      - Bowlene, 1931-1932, (2 folders) (Box 149)
      - Brillo, 1928-1946, (9 folders) (Box 149)
      - Climax, 1930 (Box 149)
      - Dawn, 1929 (Box 149)
      - Drano, 1933-1942, (8 folders) (Box 149)
      - Drano, 1925-1932, (2 folders) (Box 150)
      - Flusho, 1941 (Box 150)
      - Gold Dust, 1923-1933, (9 folders) (Box 150)
      - Gre Solvent, 1929-1930 (Box 150)
      - Kitchen Klenzer, 1933-1936, (2 folders) (Box 150)
      - Kirkman, 1941 (Box 150)
      - Gillett's, 1933-1934 (Box 150)
      - Bab-O, 1930 (Box 150)
      - Bon Ami, 1925 (Box 150)
  - Electrical Goods
    - Household
      - Washing machines and driers, 1953 (Box 150)
      - Emerson Electric, 1947 (Box 150)
    - Industrial and institutional
      - General Electric, 1943-1944, (2 folders) (Box 150)
      - General Electric, 1942-1953, (10 folders) (Box 151)
      - Emerson Electric, 1949-1952, (3 folders) (Box 151)
      - McGraw Electric/Toastmaster, 1947-1951, (3 folders) (Box 151)
      - Mixers and blenders miscellaneous, 1954 (Box 151)
      - Proctor, 1947-1953, (7 folders) (Box 151)
      - Sunbeam, 1948-1953, (4 folders) (Box 151)
      - Universal, 1952-1953, (2 folders) (Box 151)
      - Westinghouse, 1943 (Box 151)
  - Beverages
    - Wines miscellaneous, 1946 (Box 152)
  - Industrial and institutional
    - General Electric, 1941, 1948, (2 folders) (Box 152)
    - Westinghouse, 1942-1949, (5 folders) (Box 152)
    - Bulbs and lamps--Sylvania, 1953 (Box 152)
  - Household
    - General Electric, 1947-1953, (3 folders) (Box 152)
    - McGraw Electric/Toastmaster, 1952-1953, (2 folders) (Box 152)
    - Miscellaneous, 1948-1951, (4 folders) (Box 152)
    - Sunbeam, 1947, 1951, (2 folders) (Box 152)
    - Washing machines and driers, 1954 (Box 152)
    - Westinghouse, 1949-1950, (3 folders) (Box 152)
    - Emerson Electric, 1953 (Box 153)
    - Washing machines and driers
      - Miscellaneous, 1948-1952, (6 folders) (Box 153)
      - Easy, 1947-1953, (7 folders) (Box 153)
      - Frigidaire, 1948-1953, (6 folders) (Box 153)
      - General Electric, 1947-1953, (7 folders) (Box 153)
      - Launderall, 1947-1953, (7 folders) (Box 153)
      - Maytag, 1947-1953, (7 folders) (Box 153)
      - Thor, 1947-1953, (5 folders) (Box 153)
      - Westinghouse, 1950-1953, (7 folders) (Box 153)
  - Clocks, 1951 (Box 153)
  - Industrial and institutional
    - Westinghouse, 1950-1953, (4 folders) (Box 153)
  - Household Goods
    - Floor covering
      - Linoleum and tile
        - Armstrong, 1954 (Box 153)
        - Miscellaneous, 1954 (Box 153)
      - Rugs and carpet
        - Alexander Smith, 1948-1951, (3 folders) (Box 154)
        - Bigelow, 1948-1954, (6 folders) (Box 154)
        - Gullistan, 1948-1954, (7 folders) (Box 154)
        - James Lees & Sons, 1941954, (7 folders) (Box 154)
        - Masland, 1951-1952, (2 folders) (Box 154)
        - Mohawk, 1949-1954, (4 folders) (Box 154)
        - Olson, 1952 (Box 154)
        - Miscellaneous, 1951-1954, (4 folders) (Box 154)
        - Miscellaneous, 1947-1949, (3 folders) (Box 155)
    - Floor coverings miscellaneous, 1947-1952, (5 folders)
      - Linoleum and tile
        - Armstrong, 1950-1952, (3 folders) (Box 155)
        - Miscellaneous, 1947-1952, (4 folders) (Box 155)
    - Furniture
      - Daystrom, 1954 (Box 155)
    - Fuel (See also Public Utilities)
      - Coal, Coke, etc., 1942-1946, (6 folders) (Box 155)
      - Kopper's Coke, 1939-1942, (2 folders) (Box 155)
      - Gas, 1942-1946, (4 folders) (Box 155)
      - Oil, 1945-1950, (5 folders) (Box 155)
      - Miscellaneous, 1937-1954, (7 folders) (Box 155)
    - Furniture
      - Miscellaneous, 1945-1954, (9 folders) (Box 156)
      - Daystrom, 1949-1953, (5 folders) (Box 156)
      - Drexel, 1950-1954, (5 folders) (Box 156)
      - Kroehler, 1953-1954, (2 folders) (Box 156)
      - Kroehler, 1949-1952, (4 folders) (Box 157)
      - Lane Cedar Chest, 1950-1954, (5 folders) (Box 157)
      - Mengel, 1950-1952, (3 folders) (Box 157)